<StudyFieldsResponse>
  <APIVrs>1.01.05</APIVrs>
  <DataVrs>2023:12:13 00:00:21.569</DataVrs>
  <Expression>heart attack</Expression>
  <NStudiesAvail>475971</NStudiesAvail>
  <NStudiesFound>10244</NStudiesFound>
  <MinRank>2</MinRank>
  <MaxRank>21</MaxRank>
  <NStudiesReturned>20</NStudiesReturned>
  <FieldList>
    <Field>NCTId</Field>
    <Field>BriefTitle</Field>
    <Field>Condition</Field>
    <Field>EligibilityCriteria</Field>
  </FieldList>
  <StudyFieldsList>
    <StudyFields Rank="2">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT01874691</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>China Acute Myocardial Infarction Registry</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Eligible patients must be admitted within 7 days of acute ischemic symptoms and diagnosed acute ST-elevation or non ST-elevation myocardial infarction. Diagnosis criteria must meet Universal Definition for AMI (2012). All participating hospitals are required to enroll consecutive patients with AMI.

Exclusion Criteria:

Myocardial infarction related to percutaneous coronary intervention and coronary artery bypass grafting.</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="3">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT03015064</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Post-Myocardial Infarction Patients in Santa Catarina, Brazil - Catarina Heart Study</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Age over 18 years;
Presence of precordial pain suggestive of acute myocardial infarction associated with electrocardiogram with new ST segment elevation in two contiguous leads with limits: ≥0.1 mv in all leads other than leads V2-V3 where the following limits apply : ≥0.2 mv in Men ≥40 years; ≥0.25 mV in men &lt;40 years, or ≥ 0.15 mV in women or presence of precordial pain suggestive of acute myocardial infarction associated with elevation of troponin I or CK-MB above the 99th percentile of the upper reference limit

Exclusion Criteria:

Previous acute myocardial infarction;
Disagreement with the Terms of Informed Consent.</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="4">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT01168609</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Left Atrial Distensibility and Left Ventricular Filling Pressure in Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Myocardial infarction was detected by the presence of at least two of the following criteria: chest pain lasting more than 30 minutes, typical electrocardiographic changes, and elevated creatinine kinase-MB fraction. Consecutive patients 18 years of age or older who presented within 12 hours after the onset of acute myocardial infarction were considered for enrollment.

Exclusion Criteria:

1) presence of mitral stenosis or prosthetic mitral valves
2) more than mild severity of aortic/mitral valvular problem
3) any abnormality of atrial septum (e.g., atrial septal defect or aneurysm)
4) rhythm other than sinus rhythm
5) inadequate image quality
6) lack of informed consent</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="5">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT06038994</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Prognostic Value of Surem TRAF3IP2 Level in Patients With Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction, Acute</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Patients with acute myocardial infarction
patients received coronary angiography
invasive management within 72 h of hospital admission

Exclusion Criteria:

NYHA III-IV
malignant tumor
acute infection
thyroid dysfunction
Life expectancy of b1 y
Unsuitable for PCI</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="6">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT03412435</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Asan Medical Center Myocardial Infarction Registry</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction, Acute</FieldValue>
        <FieldValue>Coronary Stenosis</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

All consecutive acute myocardial infarction patients diagnosed through coronary angiography</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="7">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT04628104</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>CMR Findings in COVID-19 Patients Presenting With Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Patients presenting with symptoms and ECG indicative of acute MI (both STEMI &amp; NSTEMI) AND confirmed COVID-19.
Patients admitted with acute MI (both STEMI &amp; NSTEMI) who develop COVID-19 symptoms during hospital admission &amp; are confirmed by RT-PCR to have COVID-19

Exclusion Criteria:

History of previous diagnosis of STEMI or myocarditis.
History of previous PCI in infarcted related artery or NSTEMI
Severe respiratory distress that precludes lying supine in the CMR scanner.
Acute kidney injury with rapidly declining GFR or GFR that is persistently below 30 ml/min/1.73 m2 (contraindication for Gadopentetate dimeglumine contrast).</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="8">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT00632788</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>The Influence of Acute Myocardial Infarction Checklist on the Door-to-Balloon Time</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

all patients who presented to the emergency department of Far Eastern Memorial Hospital within 12 hours of the onset of ischemic chest pain
patients with diagnostic criteria of acute ST-elevation myocardial infarction on electrocardiogram, e.g. at least 0.1 mV in two or more contiguous electrocardiographic leads or a new onset of bundle branch block
patients were preparing for emergency cardiac catheterization

Exclusion Criteria:

patients who did not fulfill the diagnostic criteria of acute myocardial infarction on electrocardiogram
patients who were not eligible for cardiac catheterization
patients who refused cardiac catheterization
patients who suffered from acute myocardial infarction after admission to ward or intensive care unit for any reason
patients who had an ambiguous diagnosis that the decision of emergency cardiac catheterization was made after admission to ward or intensive care unit</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="9">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT01484158</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Gait Speed for Predicting Cardiovascular Events After Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Clinical diagnosis of ST-segment elevation acute myocardial infarction
Must be treated within 12 hours after symptom onset
Must be able to walk
Must receive successful primary percutaneous coronary intervention

Exclusion Criteria:

History of prior myocardial infarction
Cerebrovascular disease with residual hemiplegia
Severe peripheral arterial disease</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="10">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT00888537</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Wiser Choices in Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Between the ages of 18 and 90
Hospitalized at Saint Marys Hospital
A primary diagnosis of AMI,
Have heart rate, blood pressure, troponin and creatinine measurements,
There is an intention to offer treatment medications
Are able and willing to provide informed consent

Exclusion Criteria:

Have not had a myocardial infarction
Have significant cognitive, visual impairment,
Non-English speaker
Have a Do Not Intubate/Do Not Resuscitate (DNI/DNR) status
Will be discharged to a nursing home
AMI is not the presumptive diagnosis</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="11">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT05090618</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>The Role of Genetic Factors in the Development of Myocardial Infarction in the Kazakh Population</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Heart Attack</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Persons of Kazakh nationality
Age up to 59 years inclusive at the time of primary myocardial infarction
Myocardial infarction was established in accordance with the EOC criteria: An increase and / or decrease in the level of cardiac troponin must be combined with at least one of the following: • Symptoms of myocardial ischemia • Newly occurring ischemic changes on the ECG • The appearance of a pathological Q wave • Identification according to imaging data methods of new areas of non-viable myocardium, or new areas of local contractility disorders of presumably ischemic etiology • Detection of a thrombus in the coronary arteries according to coronary angiography
Presence of coronary angiography
Persons able and willing to provide written informed consent;

Exclusion Criteria:

Age at primary myocardial infarction 60 years and older
Heart defects, congenital and acquired
Non-ischemic cardiomyopathies
Autoimmune diseases
Diabetes mellitus at the time of development of primary myocardial infarction
Terminal stages of renal and hepatic failure</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="12">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT01109225</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Relation Between Aldosterone and Cardiac Remodeling After Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Man or woman hospitalized for a first myocardial infarction with known shift of the segment ST revascularized in acute phase by primary angioplasty and dated less than 4 days
Patient presenting a stable clinical state
Patient presenting a regular sinusal cardiac rhythm
Patient having an age ≥ 18 years

Exclusion Criteria:

Counter-indication with examination MRI
Severe claustrophobia
Antecedent of over-sensitiveness to gadolinium salts
Nonischaemic Cardiopathy
Cardiac surgery planed in the 6 months
Women into old to procreate without effective contraception</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="13">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT02913820</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Association of Snowfall and Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

myocardial infarction being confirmed or treated in the cathlab

Exclusion Criteria:

none</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="14">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT03022552</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Heart Attack Research Program: Platelet Sub-Study (HARP)</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Acute ischemic symptoms compatible with diagnosis of MI, such as chest pain or anginal equivalent symptoms at rest or new onset exertional anginal equivalent symptoms

Objective evidence of MI (either or both of the following):

Elevation of troponin to above the laboratory upper limit of normal (ULN)
ST segment elevation of ≥1mm on 2 contiguous ECG leads
Willing to provide informed consent and comply with all aspects of the protocol
Administration of aspirin at least 1 hour before cardiac catheterization
Administration of thienopyridine (e.g., clopidogrel, ticagrelor) at least 1 hour before cardiac catheterization
Women and men with ≥50% of any major epicardial vessel on invasive angiography may participate

Exclusion Criteria:

Recent use of vasospastic agents, such as cocaine, triptans, or ergot alkaloids (≤1 month)
Alternate explanation for troponin elevation, such as hypertensive urgency, acute exacerbation of heart failure, chronic elevation due to kidney disease, pulmonary embolism, cardiac trauma
Pregnancy
Thrombolytic therapy for STEMI (qualifying event)
Use of any of the following medications:
Platelet antagonists (except aspirin and thienopyridines) within 7 days
NSAIDs (e.g., ibuprofen, naproxen) within 3 days.
Thrombocytopenia (platelet count &lt;100,000)
Thrombocytosis (platelet count &gt;500,000)
Anemia (hemoglobin &lt;9 mg/dl)
Hemorrhagic diathesis</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="15">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT02072850</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Detection and Significance of Heart Injury in ST Elevation Myocardial Infarction.</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Acute ST-elevation Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Acute STEMI

Exclusion Criteria:

Major systemic illness (e.g. cancer limiting survival &lt; 6 months);
Metallic implant (e.g. cochlear implant);
Metallic foreign body
Pregnancy.</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="16">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT00597922</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Examining Heart Attacks in Young Women</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Elevated cardiac markers within 24 hours of arrival at initial or enrolling institution
Supporting evidence suggestive of a heart attack

Exclusion Criteria:

Previously enrolled in the VIRGO study
Does not speak English or Spanish
Too ill to interview
Current prisoner</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="17">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT01182064</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Acute Myocardial Infarction by Penetrating Cardiac Trauma</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Heart stab Injury

Exclusion Criteria:

Previous cardiac injuries, coronary artery disease with previous diagnostic, previous coronary angiography (for any indication)</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="18">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT04957719</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Selatogrel Outcome Study in Suspected Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Main Inclusion Criteria:

Confirmed diagnosis of symptomatic type 1 acute myocardial infarction (AMI) ST-Elevation Myocardial Infarction (STEMI) or Non-ST-Elevation Myocardial Infarction (NSTEMI), no longer than 4 weeks prior to randomization.

Diagnosis of multivessel coronary artery disease defined as ≥ 50% stenosis on 2 or more coronary artery territories or on the left main artery during a prior cardiac catheterization or cardiac catheterization during the qualifying AMI event and presence of at least 2 of the following risk factors:

Second prior AMI,
Diabetes mellitus defined by ongoing glucose lowering treatment,
Chronic kidney disease with estimated glomerular filtration rate less-than 60 mL/min/1.73 m2,
Peripheral artery disease at any time prior to randomization,
Absence of, or unsuccessful coronary revascularization of the qualifying AMI.
Successful self-administered placebo according to the autoinjector instruction for use training during screening.

Main Exclusion Criteria:

Increased risk of serious bleeding including any of the following:

History of intracranial bleed at any time.
Known uncorrected intracranial vascular abnormality.
Gastrointestinal bleed requiring hospitalization or transfusion within 1 year prior to screening.
Already on oral triple antithrombotic therapy (i.e., Dual antiplatelet therapy and oral anticoagulant).
Known liver impairment significantly affecting the hepatic function.
Current dialysis.
Ischemic stroke or transient ischemic attack within 3 months of screening.
Chronic anemia with hemoglobin &lt; 10 g/dL.
Chronic thrombocytopenia with platelet count &lt; 100,000/mm3.
Known hypersensitivity to selatogrel, any of its excipients, or drugs of the P2Y12 class.
Previous exposure to an investigational drug within 3 months prior to randomization.
Participation in another clinical trial with an investigational product or device within 3 months prior to randomization.</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="19">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT04050163</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>MiSaver® Stem Cell Treatment for Heart Attack (Acute Myocardial Infarction)</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Patients aged 20~80
Acute Myocardial Infarction 1 to 10 days
Cardiac enzyme CK-MB or Troponin &gt; 2X of high-end normal value
ST-elevation on EKG (STEMI)
Presence of regional wall motion abnormality
Left ventricular ejection fraction (LVEF) of ≤40%
Hemodynamically stable past 24 hour
Participants with adequate pulmonary function
Peripheral artery oxygen saturation ≥97%
Karnofsky performance status scores of ≥60.

Exclusion Criteria:

Age &lt;20 or &gt;80
Pregnant or breast feeding
Positive adventitious infections (such as HIV, hepatitis )
Revascularization via coronary artery bypass surgery is required
Coronary revascularization procedures is anticipated during the 6-month study period
Severe aortic or mitral valve narrowing
Evidence of life-threatening arrhythmia on baseline electrocardiogram (ECG)
Short of breath unable to receive PCI examination or treatment
Malignant tumor
Hematopoietic dysplasia
Severe organ disease
With less than 1 year of life expectancy
Chronic kidney disease with CCr&lt;20ml/min
Kidney disease on renal dialysis</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="20">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT01150825</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Feasibility of High Frequency QRS Analysis in Patients With Acute Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Age &gt; 40 years (men and women)
Time from onset of chest pain ≤ 12h
AMI confirmed by biomarkers
Clinical or electrocardiographic evidence of ischemia during recording
Signed an informed consent

Exclusion Criteria:

Prior MI
Prior CABG
pre-excitation syndrome (e.g. WP)
Atrial Fibrillation or significant ventricular arrhythmia
BBB, intraventricular conduction delay or QRS duration &gt; 120 ms
Implanted pacemaker or defibrillator
Left-ventricular hypertrophy</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
    <StudyFields Rank="21">
      <FieldValues Field="NCTId">
        <FieldValue>NCT01936675</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="BriefTitle">
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction Genes (MI-GENES) Study</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="Condition">
        <FieldValue>Coronary Artery Disease</FieldValue>
        <FieldValue>Myocardial Infarction</FieldValue>
        <FieldValue>Genomic Risk Communication</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
      <FieldValues Field="EligibilityCriteria">
        <FieldValue>Inclusion Criteria:

Patients between the ages of 45-70 years
Patients who have participated in the Mayo Clinic Biobank or a previous research study at Mayo Clinic
Patients who live in Southeast Minnesota

Exclusion Criteria:

Taking statin or other lipid lowering medications
Patients with a history of myocardial infarction, coronary artery disease, or other atherosclerotic medical conditions</FieldValue>
      </FieldValues>
    </StudyFields>
  </StudyFieldsList>
</StudyFieldsResponse>
